Mahardika Kharisma Ajie

I'm a Frontend Developer with more than 3 years experience using React, Laravel, Tailwind, etc. I also used to work remotely and keep good communication with the team. I love to learn new things in order to keep my skills updated in programming.

Email: mahardikakharisma@gmail.com

Phone: 6281314721632

Pekanbaru City, Riau, Indonesia



Work Experiences

Frontend Developer

PT. Juke Solutions • June 2023 - Present

Involved in the process of developing the education data collection system at the Indonesian Ministry of Religion called EMIS. The technologies used are React Native, Gitlab, and Jira.

Frontend Developer

PT. Solusi Data Madani • August 2020 - June 2023

Involved in the development process of a village administration application called Digidesa. The technologies used are React JS, Git, Bootstrap, jQuery, and Jest. Apart from that, I was also involved in the process of developing the village's profile web and web-based school administration applications using Laravel, Livewire, and MySQL.

Mentor

Flashsoft Indonesia • July 2019 - December 2019

Teach private programming courses using Yii2.

JUK D

Education

UIN Sultan Syarif Kasim Riau

Informatics Engineering • 2015 - 2020

I conducted research on the use of the FP-Growth algorithm on the weighing results of goods vehicles in Riau, Indonesia.

Skills

Javascript, React JS, React Native, Git, Scrum, Agile Methodologies, HTML, CSS, Typescript, Next JS, PHP, Laravel, Tailwind, Bootstrap, SASS/SCSS, jQuery, Laravel, Codelgniter, and Livewire.



Languages

- Indonesia Native
- English Intermediate

Powered by CakeResume